Guide to the Daniel Rubin Papers TAM.657
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Post-1991 Communist Party Split, 1991-2015; 37 Linear Feet in 77 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 4 cassette boxes; 71 audiocassettes; 2.54 Gigabytes in 1030 computer files
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Forum, 2012 (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Fundamentals Standards Group, 2005 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Lists (Restricted), 2010-2013 (Box 242, Folder 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access to folder 1 is restricted until 2068.
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Mailings, 2002-2004 (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Mass Issues, 2004 (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: People's Weekly World Forum, 2011 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: People's Weekly World Forum: Letters and Flyers Sent Out, 2001-2012 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: People's Weekly World Forum: Local Elections, 2009-2011 (Box 162, Folder 4-5)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Plan of Work, undated (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party: China, 1997 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: Club Conference: Mora Report, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: Club Conference, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: Club Education, 2007-2008, 2011, 2015; TW_TAM_657_ER_10
  - Communist Party: Club Education: Youth, 2004 (Box 162, Folder 10-11)
  - Communist Party: Club Education: Youth, 2004-2005 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: Club Email Blasts, 2013 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: Club Materials, 2003-2004 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: Club Meeting: "Join the Communist Party" Cards, 2002 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Commentaries, 1999 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: Constitution: Preamble, 2006 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 25th:Gus Hall After Convention, 1991-1993 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 25th: Supporters After Convention, 1991 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th, 2005 (Box 163, Folder 9-10)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th, 2005 (Box 164, Folder 1-2)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Discussion Bulletins, 38412 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: Convention, Draft of Basic Party Program: Discussion Outline, 2005 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Late Program Proposals, 2005 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Party Program Drafts, 2005 January (Box 164, Folder 6-8)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Party Program Draft: Correspondence, 2005 February-March (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Party Program Draft: Rubin Edits, 2005 (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Party Program Draft: Program Committee: Correspondence, 2005 (Box 164, Folder 11-12)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Party Program Draft: The Road to Socialism, 2005
    - Paper Materials (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_11
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Party Program Draft: The Road to Socialism USA, 2005 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Party Program Draft: Rubin Edits, 2005 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Planning Notes and Correspondence, 2005 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Program Draft - Final, 38504 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Report to the Working Group to Draft a New Party Program, 38381 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Resolution, 2005 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Young Communist League, 2005 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 28th: Program Procedure, 2005 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 29th, 2010 (Box 165, Folder 9-11)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 29th, 2009-2010 (Box 166, Folder 1-2)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 29th: Discussions, 2010 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 30th, 2014 (Box 166, Folder 4-7)
  - Communist Party: Convention, 30th: Documents, 2014 (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: Conventions, 2009-2014; TW_TAM_657_ER_12
  - Communist Party: Correspondence: Student Thesis on CPUSA Leadership, 2010 (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: Education, 2005-2008 (Box 166, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: Education, 2005-2013 (Box 167, Folder 1-4)
  - Communist Party: Education: African American History, 2014-2015 (Box 167, Folder 5-6)
  - Communist Party: Education: African American History: Exhibits, 2015 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: Education: Assessment and Notes, 2014 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: Education: Club and District: Historical Materialism, circa 2000s (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: Education: Club Education Program Guide, 2003 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: Education Commission, 2006 April-December (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Education Commission: Club Education Guides and Study Guides, 2002-2008 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: Education Commission: Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party: Education: Correspondence, 2008-2014 (Box 168, Folder 7-11)
  - Communist Party: Education: Discussion Group on Socialism, 2011 (Box 168, Folder 12)
  - Communist Party: Discussion Groups, 2009, 2011 (Box 168, Folder 13)
  - Communist Party: Education: District and Club Leadership Schools, 2001-2002 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: Education: District Organizers Workshop, 2003 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: Education: For Educators, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: Education: Forum for African American History, 2008 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Education: Leadership Seminar, 2002 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: Education: Leadership Training, 2012-2013 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party: Education: Marxist Methodology: Discussion Group, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: Education: Marxist Methodology: Discussion Group Series, 2013, 2015
    - Paper Materials (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_13
  - Communist Party: Education: National District Leaders Seminar, 2004 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: Education: National School, 2002-2009, 2013
    - Paper Materials (Box 169, Folder 10-11, Box 170, Folder 1-3)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_14
  - Communist Party: Education: National School Curriculum, 2009 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Education: National School Evaluations, 2009 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: Education: National School Materials, 2009 (Box 170, Folder 6-7)
  - Communist Party: Education: National School Reading, 2009 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: Education: National School Registration, 2009 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: Education: National School Teachers, 2009 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: Education: National School Set Up, 2009 (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Communist Party: Education: National School Students, 2009 (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - Communist Party: Education: National Youth School: General, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: Education: National Youth School: Groups, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 2-3)
  - Communist Party: Education: National Youth School: Participants, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Education: National Youth School: Reading, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: Education: National Youth School: Reading and Forms, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party: Education: National Youth School: Teaching, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: Education: National Youth School, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 8-9)
  - Communist Party: Education: National Youth School: Students, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: Education: National Youth School: Teaching, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - Communist Party: Education: New Member Education, 1988, 2003, 2007-2009
    - Paper Materials (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_15
  - Communist Party: Education: New York New Member School, 2011 (Box 171, Folder 13)
  - Communist Party: Education: Notes for Communism Class, undated (Box 171, Folder 14)
  - Communist Party: Education: Old Education Outlines, 2004 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: Education: Outlines for Discussion Series, 2009 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: Education: People's Weekly World Educational Articles and Booklets, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: Education: Regional Schools: New York and Illinois, 2003 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Education: Seminar on Party, 2011 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: Education: Seminar on Youth Question, undated (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party: Education: Session Materials, circa 2011 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: Education: Strategy and Tactics Discussion Group, 2010 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: Education: Students, 2012 (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: Education: Study Group Guide, 1982, 2005 (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: Education: Study Group Materials, 2009 (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - Communist Party: Education: Summer Classes, 2008 (Box 172, Folder 12)
  - Communist Party: Education: What is Marxism Class, 2014-2015
    - Paper Materials (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_16
  - Communist Party: Education: Young Communist League Session, 2011 (Box 172, Folder 14)
  - Communist Party: Elections, 2001-2003, 2010, 2012
    - Paper Materials (Box 172, Folder 15-16)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_17
  - Communist Party: Elections Report, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: General Politics, 2013 January-April (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: ITs Finances Moscow Gold, 1992 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: Jerez vs. Republic of Cuba, 2009 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Jewish Commission, 2007-2010 (Box 173, Folder 5-8)
  - Communist Party: Jewish Question: Correspondence, 2006 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: Leadership: Correspondence, 2010 (Box 173, Folder 10-11)
  - Communist Party: Left Critics, 38504 (Box 174, Folder 1-2)
  - Communist Party: Lists and Mailings (Restricted), 2002-2003 (Box 242, Folder 2-3)
    Access to folders 2-3 is restricted until 2068.
  - Communist Party: Lists for United and Renew Party Initiative (Restricted), 1991 (Box 242, Folder 4)
    Access to folder 4 is restricted until 2068.
  - Communist Party: Miscellaneous Discussion / Seminar Materials, 2008-2009 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: Miscellaneous Emails, 2009 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Miscellaneous Materials (Conventions, National Committee), 2000-2001 (Box 174, Folder 5-6)
  - Communist Party: Miscellaneous Materials (Conventions, National Committee), 2000-2001 (Box 174, Folder 7-9)
  - Communist Party: Mora, Elena: Reports, 2008 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: Mora, Elena: Correspondence, 2008 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - Communist Party: National, 2005-2006 (Box 175, Folder 1-7)
  - Communist Party: National, 2008-2009 (Box 176, Folder 1-3)
  - Communist Party: National: Report, 2007 (Box 176, Folder 4-7)
  - Communist Party: National: Strategy and Tactics Paper - Final, 2006 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: National Board, 2012-2013 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: National Board and National Committee, 1992 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: National Chairman: Reports and Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: National Committee: Report on Elections, 2004 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: National Committee: Sam Webb Report, 2008-2011
    - Paper Materials (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_18
  - Communist Party: National Committee Meeting: Reports, 2004, 2011
    - Paper Materials (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_19
  - Communist Party: National Committee and Club Conference, 2002 (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: National Committee and National Board, 2005-2009 (Box 177, Folder 9-12)
  - Communist Party: National Committee and National Board, 2008-2010 (Box 178, Folder 1-12)
  - Communist Party: National Committee and National Board, 2011-2015 (Box 179, Folder 1-8)
  - Communist Party: National Committee and National Board: Graphs, 2003-2005 (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: National Council, 2013 January-November (Box 179, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: National Council, 2013 March-July (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: National Council and National Board, 2011-2012 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: National Education, undated (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: National Leadership: Webb, Sam, 2003-2004 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: National Organizing Department: Correspondence, 2004 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: National Question, 2002 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party: New Member Class, 39326 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: New Members Orientation, 2013 (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: New York Clubs: Addresses (Restricted), 2011 (Box 242, Folder 5-6)
    Access to folders 5-6 is restricted until 2068.
  - Communist Party: New York Clubs, 2007-2015 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: New York Clubs: Conference, 2010 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: New York Clubs: Club Conference, 2002 (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - Communist Party: New York Clubs: Education: Working Class, 2007 (Box 180, Folder 12)
  - Communist Party: New York Clubs: Club and Executive Committee Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 180, Folder 13)
  - Communist Party: New York Club Lists (Restricted), 2004-2008 (Box 242, Folder 7-8)
    Access to folders 7-8 is restricted until 2068.
  - Communist Party: New York Clubs: Club Meeting, 2014 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: New York Clubs: Leaflets, 2002-2003 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: New York Clubs: Park Slope: General, 2003 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: New York Clubs: Party Communications for Clubs, 2002-2003 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: New York Club: Schools, undated (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: New York Club: Discussions on the Economy, 2011-2012 (Box 181, Folder 6-7)
  - Communist Party: New York City: Discussions on the Economy, 2012 (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: New York City: Mayoralty, Reports, etc., 2013 (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - Communist Party: New York City Economic Report, 2009 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: New York City Economy, 2009 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: New York City and State: Mass Developments, 2011-2012 (Box 181, Folder 12)
  - Communist Party: New York District, 2003 (Box 181, Folder 13)
  - Communist Party: New York District: Development Report, 2007-2008 (Box 181, Folder 14)
  - Communist Party: New York District: Development Report, 2007-2008 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: New York District: Correspondence, 2007-2010 (Box 182, Folder 4-10)
  - Communist Party: New York District: Correspondence, 2008-2011 (Box 183, Folder 1-3)
  - Communist Party: New York State, 2005-2014 (Box 183, Folder 4-8)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Better World Awards: Introduction to Major Owens, 2006 (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Better World Awards: Introduction to Letitia James, 2009 (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: New York State, 2005-2015 (Box 184, Folder 1-9)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Better World Awards, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Convention, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 2-3)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Convention, 28th, 2005 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Convention Organizing, Commission Meeting, 2010 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Education, 1995-2008 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Educational Work, 2014-2015 (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Marxism Classes, 2015 (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Member Lists and People's Weekly World / Political Affairs Subscriptions (Restricted), circa 2008 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Outreach and "Mobilizer" Lists (Restricted), undated (Box 241, Folder 2)
    Access to folder 2 is restricted until 2068.
  - Communist Party: New York State, 2005-2013 (Box 186, Folder 1-5)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Convention, 2010 (Box 186, Folder 6-7)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Convention, 30th, 2014 (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Convention, 30th: Agenda, 2014 (Box 186, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Convention, 30th: Differences and Discussion, 2014 (Box 186, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Convention, 30th: Keynote and Discussion, 2014 (Box 186, Folder 11)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Education, 2014-2015 (Box 186, Folder 12)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Education: African American History Series, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Labor, 2006 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Panel, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: New York State: Resolutions, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: On Israel and Palestine, 2013 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: On National Elections, 2008 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party: On Party Organization, 2004 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: Pamphlets, 2004-2010 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: Party Builder and Action Alert, 2002 (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: People's World, 2014-2015, undated (Box 187, Folder 10-11)
  - Communist Party: Program: Party Evolution, 2005 (Box 187, Folder 12)
  - Communist Party: Report on Working Class, 2000 (Box 187, Folder 13)
  - Communist Party: Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 187, Folder 14)
  - Communist Party: Rules of Order, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: Speakers, Appreciations, 2011-2012 (Box 187, Folder 15-16)
  - Communist Party: Strategy and Tactics, 2010-2013
    - Paper Materials (Box 187, Folder 17)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_20
  - Communist Party: Strategy and Tactics: By Phone, 2012 (Box 187, Folder 18)
  - Communist Party: Strategy and Tactics: Discussion Group, 2012 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party: Tribute to Henry Winston, 2012 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party: Webb, Sam: Report and Convention, 2013 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Communist Parties of the World, 1995 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party and Left History, 1999 (Box 181, Folder 9)
  - CPUSA Estimate: Danny Rubin, Jim Jackson, Lou Diskin, Jim Steele, 1993 February 27 (Box 236, Cassette 116-117)
  - CPUSA on International Affairs, 1994 March 29 (Box 238, Cassette 196-197)
  - Correspondence: Personal and Memorials, 2006-2014
    - Paper Materials (Box 188, Folder 4-13, Box 189, Folder 1-3)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_21
  - Cuba, 1999 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Cylich, Bernie, 2001 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - The Day the Party Donned White Sheets by Arlene Tyner, 2006 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA), 1994-1999 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) Left Organization Proposal, 1997 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Differences in Ruling Class, 2002 (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - Diskin, Bernice: Misleads of Bush, 2001 (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - Diskin, Lou: Writings, 2001, undated (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Diskin, Lou and Bernice Wills, 2003 (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Discussion Ends: Tape 2, 1997 January 12 (Box 237, Cassette 165)
  - Discussion Group Materials, 1997-2001 (Box 190, Folder 3-4)
  - Domestic Situation, 1994 July 6 (Box 235, Cassette 101-102)
  - Domestic War on Terrorism News Clippings, circa 2002 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Economy of Socialism, 2001 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Economy of Socialism, 2002 January 6 (Box 236, Cassette 138)
  - Economy of Socialism: MDG, 2002 January 6 (Box 236, Cassette 139-141)
  - Economic Market Under Socialism, 1991 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Education: Brooklyn Friends School, 1997-1998 (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Education: The Kids, etc., 1997 (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - Education for Jason and Hector, 1997 (Box 190, Folder 10-11)
  - Education for Jason and Hector, 2000 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Education Fund and Socialist Project, 1999 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Elections, 1998 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Elections: 3rd Parties, 1996 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Elections: National Politics, 2004 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Electoral Independence (Political), 1999 (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Electoral for Jim Steele, 1993 June 21 (Box 238, Cassette 201)
  - Electoral Legislative Bills, Elected Officials, 2003 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - Electoral Policy: Jay Opens, 1998 November 1 (Box 238, Cassette 204)
  - Electoral Policy: MDG, 1998 November 1 (Box 238, Cassette 205)
  - Electoral Politics: Labor, Demo Orbit, 1998 (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - Elena, 2002 (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - Essays by Daniel Rubin, 2000-2011 (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - Event Flyers and Information, 2007-2013; TW_TAM_657_ER_22
  - "Excerpts from The Works of Marx and Lenin" by Daniel Rubin, 1999 (Box 191, Folder 11)
  - Factionalists, 2006 (Box 191, Folder 12)
  - Fascists - United States and Reaction and the Right, 1991 (Box 191, Folder 13)
  - Faxing, 1992 (Box 191, Folder 14)
  - Fearon, Zita Materials, 2008 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Feral Art, 1999 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Finances, 2003 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Ford, Henry, 2000 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Frank, Mort, 1992 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Freedom Socialist Party, 1999 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - A Fresh Look at Marxism, undated (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - "Fundamentals of Marxism-Leninism" ed. Otto Kuusinen: Excerpt, 1962 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Fundamentals of Marxism: Original Glossary, undated (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Geneva Initiative, undated (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Globalization: MDG, 2001 September 16, November 11 (Box 235, Cassette 82-85)
  - Glossary, 2011 (Box 192, Folder 11)
  - Gluck, Sidney, 2001 (Box 192, Folder 12)
  - Green Party and Nader, 2000 (Box 192, Folder 13)
  - Hall, Gus: Deeper Look, etc., 2000 (Box 192, Folder 14)
  - Hall, Gus: On the Indian Question, Judith on Amendment, 1985 December 3 (Box 236, Cassette 133)
  - Health Technology and Eyesight, 1994 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Hill, Row, 2005 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Hill, Ron and Kimmel, Alan Correspondence, 2005 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Historical Materialism, 2000 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Historical Materialism: Tape 2, 2000 October 15 (Box 235, Cassette 86)
  - Historical Materialism: MDG: Tape 3, 2000 October 15 (Box 235, Cassette 87)
  - Historical Materialism: MDG: Tape 3, 2000 October 15 (Box 235, Cassette 88)
  - Historical Materialism: MDG: Openings by Danny Rubin: Tape 1, 2000 October 15 (Box 235, Cassette 89)
  - Historical Materialism: MDG: Openings: Tape 1, 2000 October 15 (Box 235, Cassette 90)
  - Historical Materialism: MDG: Discussion, 2000 October 15 (Box 235, Cassette 91)
  - Historical Materialism: Danny Rubin, 2003 December 4 (Box 235, Cassette 92)
  - Historians of American Communism, 1997 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Humor, undated (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Ideological Documents, 2007-2008 (Box 193, Folder 7-8)
  - Imperialism: Research, etc., 2012 (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Institute for Policy Studies and Fairness Agenda for America, 1999 (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - International Situation, Rubin, 1994 June 7-11 (Box 235, Cassette 93-95)
  - International Situation: MDG, 1999 October 31, 2000 January 9 (Box 235, Cassette 96-100)
  - International Situation, 1994, 2000 (Box 193, Folder 11-12)